

#### **Personal Information**

Age: 23

Gender: Female

#### Contact

Phone:

923364976

Email:

nardosmiiniiliik@gmail.com

Address:

166

## Language Skills

Amharic - Native, English - Fluent

# **Nardos Minilik**

## Fresh graduate

#### **About**

Motivated Electrical and Computer Engineering (Computer Engineering) graduate from Hawassa University Institute of Technology with four-month experience in software development using Asp.net MVC and developed a website for a company using React JS. Skilled in working independently or in a team and I have online certificates in different short courses. Looking with excitement to develop my work skill and provide excellent service in my workplace.

#### Education



Electrical and Computer Engineering Hawassa University

GPA: 3.41

Jul 2022 Graduation date

## Work experience



Dec 2022 - Mar 2023 3 month

#### web developer

St. Mechael Business and IT institute



Nov 2021 - Mar 2022 4 month

#### **Software** development

Hawassa university

As a web developer in their as team I participated in network installation, checking & updating the whole performance of the computers in their and also in making logo, flayer and other advertising materials because it was a startup institution and also in making the website starting from UI designing using Figma up to developing it using React JS.

In this four month internship experience me and my team develop a web application for Ekub system using ASP.net MVC frame work in just for month by learning new software tools and technologies.

#### **Certifications**

Dec 2021

Certification was issued

Nov 2021

Certification was issued

Oct 2021 Certification was issued

Sep 2021 Certification was issued

## Certificate of completion leadership training

- The alumni chapter of YALI RLC Ethiopia and American Spaces Ethiopia

The Young African Leaders Initiative certificate in Community Journalism YALINETWORK

The Young African Leaders Initiative certificate in Smart Entrepreneurship YALINETWORK

Diploma in Website Development Using HTML and CSS Alison

**derej**ä Generated by dereja.com

## **Extracurricular Activity**

Dec 2022 - Mar 2023 Web developer ST. Mechael

business and IT institute

I have greate expirence in ST. Mechael business and IT institute working as a web developer in their as team I participated in network installation, checking & updating the whole performance of the computers in their and also in making logo, flayer and other advertising materials because it was a startup institution and also in making the website starting from UI designing using Figma up to developing it using React JS.

Jul 2016 - May 2022 Customer service Agape kursakurs

Starting from 2016 in my spare time I was working at my mother small shop and cafe as a costumer service and a waitress, for me this experience taught me so many things in life and in working environment also.

### **Additional Skills**

Teamwork, Creative thinking, Analytical thinking, C#, Java, Web programming, Operating system, Network designing, Arduino programming, Excellent interpersonal skills, Html and CSS, Asp.net MVC frame work, JavaScript, React.js

#### References

Software developer

Hawassa University

Desalegn Mengesha

Lecture in Hawassa university

Hawassa university

Abeto Alemu

Contact detail:

0911035690

Contact detail:

+251910113191